<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HeatStress</string>
    <string name="Emargency_Recomendations">

        "If you are experiencing:
        1) Confusion, slurred speech
        2) Loss of consciousness
        3) Red, hot, dry skin or profuse sweating
        4) Very high body temperature
        Call your manager and 911"

    </string>

    <string name="minimal_DO_REQ">

        "Stay hydrated,  drink water even if you are not thirsty. Wear sunscreen."

    </string>

    <string name="minimal_DONT_REQ">

        "Don’t Over work, take short water brakes when feeling any discomfort."

    </string>

    <string name="medium_DO_REQ">

        "Stay hydrated,  drink water at least each 15 minutes, even if you are not thirsty. Wear sunscreen. Schedule breaks in a cool, shaded area."

    </string>

    <string name="medium_DONT_REQ">

        "Don’t Over work, take short water brakes when feeling any discomfort. Don’t spend to much time under direct sun light."

    </string>

    <string name="high_DO_REQ">

        "Stay hydrated,  drink water at least each 10 minutes, even if you are not thirsty. Wear sunscreen. Schedule frecuent breaks in a cool, shaded area, try to take them alongside with your water breaks. Limit physical exertion, use mechanical equipment when possible"

    </string>

    <string name="high_DONT_REQ">

        "Don’t Over work, take water brakes when feeling any discomfort. Don’t spend to much time under direct sun light. Don’t work alone, always be sure to tell someone where you’ll be working and the time you’ll spend there"

    </string>

    <string name="very_high_DO_REQ">
        "BE ALERT OF THE EXTREME RISK CONDITIONS
		Drink water CONSTANTLY. Apply sunscreen every couple of hours. Schedule breaks in a cool, shaded area. Use cooling techniques. Watch/communicate with workers at all times"
    </string>

    <string name="very_high_DONT_REQ">
        "Don’t Over work, take water brakes when feeling any discomfort. Don’t spend to much time under direct sun light. Don’t work alone, work along side 2 or 3 people. Stop work if necesary"
    </string>


    <string-array name="array_Subjects">
        <item>RCP</item>
        <item>Dehidration</item>
        <item>Hemlich</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
